<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Perth Linux Users Group</title>
    <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Perth Linux Users Group</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language><atom:link href="http://www.plug.org.au/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2002</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2002/</guid>
      <description>date: 11th December 2001 prez: matt kemner vice: jason nicholls secy/tres: tony breeds-taurima member/librarian: daniel beard Motion to increase committee to five.(moved leon brooks 2nded jason nicholls) - CARRIED. member: james bromberger (moved leon brooks 2nded jason nicholls) No other proposals, all seconded.
Tony B-T: TAFE - educational membership incl lecture theatre w/facilities PLUG has $600
LCA2003 - ending skyshow (sat 26jan2003) day
meetings at Blue Duck on 1st Sun of each month 9AM James B: LCA2002 - 5/6 going now due 1st week Feb 2002</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2003</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2003/</guid>
      <description>Date: Wed, 12 Feb 2003 14:32:14 +0800 (WST) From: &amp;ldquo;Anthony J. Breeds-Taurima&amp;rdquo; tony@cantech.net.au To: &amp;ldquo;P.L.U.G.&amp;rdquo; plug@plug.linux.org.au Subject: [plug] AGM last night
Hi everyone, FOr those of you that couldn&amp;rsquo;t make it along last night here is a summary of what happend. Note these are note minutes per se.
A special thanks the the annonymous author!
35/36 attendees (4/5 Fem) Apologies Harry and Jacqueline McNally Bret and Anne Busby Trevor Phillips if we forgot you I&amp;rsquo;m sorry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2004</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2004/</guid>
      <description>The Perth Linux User Group (PLUG) Annual General Meeting was held Tuesday 10 February, 2004 at the normal Tuesday meeting place, Perth Central TAFE in Northbridge. Present were:- Vice President - Bernard Blackham Secretary - Mark Gaynor OCM - Clare Johnstone OCM - Leon Brooks and twenty plus, general members. Apologies received from:- President - Tony Breeds Treasurer - Mark Tearle The meeting was officially opened at 1950Hrs with the Vice President (Bernard Blackham) welcoming everyone to the Perth Linux User Group Annual General Meeting for 2003/4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2005</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2005/</guid>
      <description>&gt;Summary for the impatient the 2005 committee are: President: Cameron Patrick Vice President: Marcus Giles Secretary: Bernard Blackham Treasurer: Mark Gaynor Ordinary Committee Members: Tim White, Ryan Smith, Greg Macham Unofficial PLUG roles are: Librarian: Nick Bannon, with assistance from James Devenish Talks coordinator: Cameron and Bernard are willing to help but further volunteers would be appreciated. Web masters: Cameron Patrick and Mark Gaynor List masters: Tim White, Cameron Patrick, James Devenish, Craig Ringer Annual General Meeting opened Mon Jan 24 19:45:34 WST 2005 Cameron Patrick takes minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2006</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2006/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2006/</guid>
      <description>Summary for the impatient The new PLUG committee for 2006 is: President: Ian Kent Vice President: Bernard Blackham Secretary: Daniel Axtens Treasurer: Mark Gaynor Ordinary Committee Members: Tim White, Jeff Rida, Marcus Giles, and Cameron Patrick Non-committee positions: Librarian: Ken Muir-Hunt List masters: Ian Kent, Mark Gaynor and Tim White Web masters: Committee to share Talks coordinator: Committee assumes responsibility Full Minutes
Meeting opened Mon Jan 30 20:08:33 WST 2006 Members Present: Marcus Giles Mark Gaynor Bernard Blackham Jim Leven Innis Cunningham Daniel Axtens Tim White James Stewart Chris Denby Jeff Rida Phil Cadwell Peter Kesners Uli Kesners Tomasz Grzegurzko Russ Powers Milan Pospisil Daniel Beard Ian Kent Arie Hol Joel Johnson Ken Muir-Hunt Apologies: Cameron Patrick Nick Bannon President&#39;s report: In absentia Vice-president&#39;s report: Nothing to report Treasurer&#39;s report: Relatively uneventful Financial membership is a little down 63 financial and 66 non-financial as of last Sunday (though many will have paid tonight) E-mail expiry warning isn&#39;t working yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2007</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2007/</guid>
      <description>Summary for the impatient The new PLUG committee for 2007 is: President: Ian Kent Vice President: Patrick Coleman Secretary: Daniel Axtens Treasurer: Mark Gaynor Ordinary Committee Members: To be appointed on-list Non-committee positions: Librarian: Ken Muir-Hunt List masters: Unchanged Web masters: Unchanged Talks coordinator: Alastair Irvine Full Minutes
Meeting opened Mon Jan 29 20:17 2007 Members present included: Bruce Axtens Daniel Axtens Tim Bowden Patrick Coleman Innis Cunningham Mark Gaynor Ian Kent John McCabe-Dansted Harry McNally Ken Muir-Hunt President&#39;s report: Nothing to report Treasurer&#39;s report: PLUG is in a solid financial position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2008</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2008/</guid>
      <description>Summary for the impatient The new PLUG committee for 2008 is: President: Patrick Coleman Vice President: Adon Metcalfe Secretary: Ian Kent Treasurer: Mark Gaynor Ordinary Committee Members: Jason Nicholls, Adrian Woodley, Ritchie Young Non-committee positions: Librarian: Lance Duivenbode List masters: Alastair Irvine, Ian Kent, Ritchie Young Web masters: Mark Gaynor, Ian Kent, Jason Nicholls, Ritchie Young Talks coordinator: Patrick Coleman, assisted by Alastair Irvine Full Minutes
Members present included: Daniel Axtens George Backlund Daniel Beard Nick Bannon Adam Chambost Patrick Coleman Innis Cunningham Mark Gaynor Alastair Irvine Joel Johnson Ian Kent Adon Metcalfe John McCabe-Dansted Jason Nicholls Nick Warren Adrian Woodley Ritchie Young Meeting opened at 21:25 PM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2009</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2009/</guid>
      <description>Summary for the impatient The new PLUG committee for 2009 is:
President: Patrick Coleman Vice President: Adon Metcalfe Secretary: Nick Sandford Treasurer: Mark Gaynor Ordinary Committee Members: Tim White, Phillip V, David L, Jason N and Peter L Non-committee positions (additions only since 2008):
Librarian: Lance Duivenbode List masters: Alastair Irvine, Ian Kent, Ritchie Young Web masters: Mark Gaynor, Ian Kent, Jason Nicholls, Ritchie Young, Msquared Talks coordinator: Patrick Coleman, assisted by Alastair Irvine Full Minutes Meeting opened at 20:00.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2010</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2010/</guid>
      <description>PLUG Annual General Meeting, 2010 Title: PLUG Annual General Meeting, 2010
When: Tuesday, 9th March 2010, 7:30pm - 9:00pm. Where: &#39;Futuresphere&#39;, Christ Church Grammar School, Queenslea Drive, Clarem ont
Summary for the impatient The new PLUG committee for 2010 is: President: Timothy White Vice President: Nick Bannon Secretary: Peter Lyons Treasurer: Mark Gaynor Ordinary Committee Members: Patrick Coleman, Alastair Irvine Full Minutes
Meeting opened Tuesday March 9th at 19:51. Members present included: Daniel Beard Nick Bannon Harry McNally Mark Gaynor George Backlund Tim White Peter Lyons Alistair Irvine Milan Pospisil Lee Potts (Visitor) Sara White (Visitor) Motion: that the minutes of the previous AGM be accepted</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2011</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2011/</guid>
      <description>Minutes of the PLUG Annual General Meeting 2011 held on Tuesday, 12th January 2011 from 7:30pm at &amp;lsquo;Futuresphere&amp;rsquo;, Christ Church Grammar School, Queenslea Drive, Claremont
Members present: Peter Lyons	(Secretary) Alastair Irvine Daniel Axtens Andrew Greig Jason Nicholls Mark Gaynor Jim Leven Arie Hol Garry Buckle Daniel Beard Harry McNally Juan J. Garcia Elena Aza Daniel J. Harmsworth Nick Bannon	(Chair) Scott Percival James Bromberger Nico Hessler
Members attending via proxy: Patrick Coleman Lance Duivenbode Tim White</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2016</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2016/</guid>
      <description>Perth Linux Users Group - Annual General Meeting 2016 - Minutes Held at 45 St Georges Terrace Perth CBD. Spacecubed.org on Tuesday 12th of January 2016 at 7:00 PM
0. Opening Meeting Opened by Michael V at 7:15 PM
16 Paid members at meeting = 16 (Margaret W, David M, Adam F, Dan B, William T, Benjamin A, James B, Craig H, Babfemi O, Michael V, Hannah S, Andrew C, Paul, James H, Paul G, Peter L, Robert W, Ican F, Mesc F, Nick B)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2017</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2017/</guid>
      <description>Perth Linux Users Group – Annual General Meeting 2017 – Minutes Held at 45 St Georges Terrace Perth CBD. Spacecubed.org on Tuesday 10th of January 2017 at 7:30 PM
0. Opening Paul opened the meeting at 19:35
1. Confirmation of Minutes of the 2016 AGM Paul proposed the minutes sent to the mailing list were true and correct.
Michael Van Delft seconded the minutes.
2. Committee Reports (including accounts) Played Video from William Termini</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2018/</guid>
      <description>Perth Linux Users Group – Annual General Meeting 2018 – Minutes The Perth Linux Users Group Annual General Meeting held at Spacecubed.com at 45 St Georges Terrace, Perth CBD on Tuesday 13th March 2018 at 7:20 PM.
0: Opening: 1920 Members present:
Paul (2017 Vice President) Peter Lyons (2017 Treasurer) Nick Bannon (2017 Secretary, AGM Chair) Margaret Wood (2017 OCM) Dean Bergin (2017 OCM) Ivan Fetwadjieff James Henstridge Harry McNally Kieran Mesquita Alastair Irvine Apologies:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2019</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2019/</guid>
      <description>Perth Linux Users Group – Annual General Meeting 2019 – Minutes The Perth Linux Users Group Annual General Meeting held at Spacecubed.com at 45 St Georges Terrace, Perth CBD on Tuesday 12th February 2019 at 19:25 PM.
Our venue has been provided by Spacecubed.com tonight.
Please add your name below if you haven’t already. We will be ordering pizza towards so let us know what you want.
0. Opening: Meeting opened at 7:25 PM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2020</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2020/</guid>
      <description>Perth Linux Users Group - Annual General Meeting 2020 - Minutes Our venue has been provided by Spacecubed.com Located at 45 St Georges Terrace, Perth WA 6000 on Tuesday 11th February 2020 at 7:00 PM. Minutes Opening. Starting 7:12 PM by Benjamin. The attendance is Nick, Margaret, Peter, Alastair, Lawrence, Paul, Patrick, Benjamin, James. Apologies from Niall and Michel. Confirmation of the minutes of the previous AGM. https://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2019/ Date: 2018 should read as 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2021</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2021/</guid>
      <description>PLUG Annual General Meeting Minutes for 2021 Venue: Spacecubed.com, 45 St Georges Terrace, Perth WA 6000 Time: Tuesday 12th January 2021 at 7:00 PM Agenda Opening.(Starting 7:00 PM sharp) Confirmation of the Minutes of the 2020 AGM Committee Reports. (Including accounts) Election of 2020 Committee. General Business. Meeting Close. 0. Meeting Opening at 19:05 PM by NB Attendance
Nick Bannon James Henstridge Paul Del Peter Lyons Margaret Wood Michael Collins Niall Navin Steve Schrader Sarah Allard Apologies Benjamin Arntzen Michel Nzikou Nick: Thanks to our venue Sponsor: Spacecubed and thanks for the use of their “Riff” space for no cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGM Archive 2022</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/AGM/2022/</guid>
      <description>PLUG Annual General Meeting 2022 Minutes Venue: Spacecubed.com, 45 St Georges Terrace, Perth WA 6000 Time: Tuesday 11th January 2022 at 7:00 PM Agenda Opening.(Starting 7:00 PM sharp) Confirmation of the Minutes of the 2021 AGM Committee Reports. (Including accounts) Election of 2021 Committee. General Business. Meeting Close. 0. Meeting Opened at 19:28 by Bemjamin Attendance Members Nick Bannon Patrick Cody Paul Del Peter Lyons Margaret Wood James Henstridge Benjamin Arntzen Steve Foreman Sarah Allard Alastair Irvine Apologies Non-members Alexander Kent 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events Archive</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/archive/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of previous PLUG events, organized by year.
2021 2020 2019 2018 2017 2016 2015 2014 2013 2012 2011 2010 2009 2008 2007 2006 2005 2004 2003 2001 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events Archive 2001</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2001/</guid>
      <description>September 11 2001 James Bromberger: Introduction to Debian (somewhat interrupted by world events!)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events Archive 2003</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2003/</guid>
      <description>January 2003 James Bromberger &amp;amp; Tony Breeds: Linux.conf.au 2003
March 2003 Tony Breeds on &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s New in 2.6&amp;rdquo;
April 2003 Hans Humboldt on &amp;ldquo;Sun&amp;rsquo;s Position in the Linux Market&amp;rdquo;
May 2003 Trent Lloyd on &amp;ldquo;User-Mode Linux (UML)&amp;rdquo;
June 2003 Bernard Blackham on &amp;ldquo;Speex Development and Applications&amp;rdquo;
July 2003 Mike Gilks on &amp;ldquo;OpenOffice.org Data Connection - databases for the rest of us&amp;rdquo;
August 2003 Sacha Schlegel on ebXML (cancelled)
September 2003 Sacha Schlegel on ebXML</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events Archive 2004</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2004/</guid>
      <description>March 2004 Bernard Blackham on &amp;ldquo;Cool Things You Should and Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t Do With PostgreSQL&amp;rdquo;
April 2004 Nick Bannon, Clare Johnstone and Cameron Patrick on linux.conf.au 2004
May 2004 Craig Ringer on &amp;ldquo;Generating quality PDF reports using Python and ReportLab&amp;rdquo;
June 2004 Leon Brooks on &amp;ldquo;Playing with Ruby-SDL&amp;rdquo;
July 2004 Bernard Blackham on &amp;ldquo;Linux, Laptops and Life&amp;rdquo;
August 2004 James Levin, Bernard Blackham and Michal Wirski presenting a post-Installfest introduction to Linux</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events Archive 2005</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2005/</guid>
      <description>March 2005 Davyd Madeley with The Clubber&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Rapid Application Development with GNOME and Python and Cameron Patrick with Software Archery: hitting the bull&amp;rsquo;s-eye with GNU Arch revision control.
April 2005 Lightning Talks
May 2005 Antics of linux.conf.au 2005
June 2005 Russell Steicke on his winning LCA 2005 hackfest entry
July 2005 Leon Brooks with a talk mysteriously entitled The Crimson Panacea
August 2005 Phil Twiss on Open Source WA and Harry McNally on Computer Angels</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events Archive 2006</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2006/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2006/</guid>
      <description>January 2006 Stuart Midgley with Linux on supercomputers &amp;amp; tour of IVEC facilities.
February 2006 Linux.conf.au 2006 reminiscing.
August 2006 Adrian Woodley on Virtual E-mail Hosting
September 2006 Adrian Chadd on Serving a gigabit of web traffic for fun and profit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events Archive 2007</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2007/</guid>
      <description>March 2007 Phil Schwan on Deconstructing Lustre
May 2007 Ian Kent on Autofs in the Linux Kernel
August 2007 Adrian Chadd on Xen and Virtualisation
September 2007 Patrick Coleman on Command Line Fu and Cameron Patrick on Map The Planet
October 2007 Adrian Woodley on Network Monitoring, and Daniel Axtens on Simple Ubuntu Tips and Tricks
November 2007 Paul Antoine on UNIX in Australia
December 2007 Davyd Madeley on Awesome Tools for Document Authoring</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events Archive 2008</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2008/</guid>
      <description>January 2008 Web Content Delivery, 2007 style, presented by Adrian Chadd
February 2008 iSCSI: It&amp;rsquo;s not a Mac, presented by Patrick Coleman
March 2008 Linux Filesystem Internals, presented by Ian Kent
April 2008 WPAD for chumps, presented by Adon Metcalfe
May 2008 LDAP for Popular People and Sysadmins, presented by Ritchie Young
June 2008 Making Emacs your bit^H^H^H preferred editor and IDE, presented by Alastair Irvine
July 2008 User security on shared hosting and shell servers, presented by David Adam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events Archive 2009</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2009/</guid>
      <description>January 2009 Heading towards single sign-on with Kerberos, presented by Nick Sandford
February 2009 AGM
March 2009 Demystifying VPNs, presented by Alastair Irvine
April 2009 MythTV: Open source content streaming, presented by Geoffrey Alagoda
May 2009 Working with Blender, presented by Innis Cunningham
July 2009 GIS on Linux, presented by Adon Metcalfe
September 2009 The Murchison Widefield Array radio telescope, presented by Dr Andrew Williams
October 2009 Proxmox VE: open-source enterprise virtualisation, presented by Adon Metcalfe</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events Archive 2010</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2010/</guid>
      <description>March 2010 AGM
May 2010 Wireless hotspots, presented by Tim White
October 2010 OpenDMX - the open DMX512 Lighting Control project, presented by Simon Newton
November 2010 Hardware - roundtable discussion on Arduino and other microcontrollers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events Archive 2011</title>
      <link>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.plug.org.au/events/2011/</guid>
      <description>January 2011 AGM
February 2011 Linux.conf.au Review, presented by Alastair
March 2011 Trip to Artifactory, presented by Daniel
Quiz night
April 2011 Harry McNally: UWA Physics Radio Telescope and Arduino
May 2011 IPv6 in the enterprise, by Carl Gharardi, at L-3 Naurtronix (download video - mp4, 234MB)
June 2011 High Performance Computing, by IBM, at IBM West Perth (download video - mp4, 276MB)
July 2011 Ubuntu One, by James Henstridge (no video sorry, audio problems)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
